Excuse me, sir. Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Multiple times.
Yeah? Quick question for you.
What do you do for a
living out here in New York City?
I work on Wall Street.
Are you a business owner?
Yes.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
49 years.
Over these 49 years, in terms of revenue,
what was the most amount of money that you
ever made in a single year at your company?
About $400 million.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yes.
Yeah?
It's fun.
What do you do for a
living out here in New York City?
Finance.
I'm on the board of five different companies.
I run seven companies.
I trade a half a billion
dollars a day of stock in there.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
If you look at the internet,
some people say I'm worth $1.8 billion.
I don't know that.
Would you give me a range, maybe?
A million.
So what is one lesson about money you
teach to somebody that the wealthy people know
that most people do not know?
One lesson about money 99% of people don't know.
Hard Knocks family, we are out in
New York City right now on Wall Street.
And today, we're going to be asking
Wall Street millionaires how they became wealthy
and the secret to becoming
financially free in today's world.
You do not want to miss out on
any of this game that's about to be given.
So stay tuned.
Until the end.
But with that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
I got no time, brother.
30 seconds.
Real quick.
I really got no time.
Hey, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
I'm still broke.
Yeah?
What do you do for a
living out in New York City?
Broke.
Yeah?
We're like, what?
We got a whole family.
Try this one.
No, she's good.
She's a business owner?
She's a financier.
Financial advisor.
Appreciate you.
Thank you, my friend.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
I started this channel at the University of Texas.
I grew it to 6 million followers.
Even though we spent hours upon
hours out on Wall Street getting rejected,
we finally ran into this guy.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
What's the best advice you've
ever gotten throughout your career?
I can't talk right now.
I'm really running late.
The best advice I ever got in my career?
Yeah.
Yes, sir.
Work hard.
The rest is overrated.
You can work hard and
work at a fast food restaurant.
30 seconds, real quick.
30 seconds.
I started a channel.
I grew it to over 6 million followers.
I've interviewed Mark Cuban, the owner of
the Texans, some of the biggest entrepreneurs.
Can I get just 30
seconds of your time, real quick?
I can't.
I'm really quick.
Okay.
Have a go with my friend.
We can't let him get away just like that.
We're going to go see if we can walk
with him and get some game for you guys.
Come on.
Let's go see what he has to say.
Hey, sir.
Sir.
Could I walk with you?
Could I walk with you and
ask you just a couple quick questions?
I'm going to this car.
What's up?
Okay.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
What do you do for a living?
Construction.
Are you a business owner?
Yes.
How long have you been an entrepreneur for?
49 years.
49 years?
What's the most common mistake
that you see business owners make?
Because 8 out of 10 businesses,
they won't make it past 5 years.
Under financed.
So what's the secret to borrowing or
getting that capital to start and grow businesses?
A lot of luck.
You know, a lot of luck.
But the safest way is to be well financed.
Yeah.
It'll help you with some bumps along the
road that are no doubt going to come.
Right.
And do you come from a lot of money?
No.
So your parents weren't wealthy.
So how did you change your family's trajectory?
What did you see out in life that
made you really want to become successful financially?
The desire to create success for myself.
And over these 49 years, in terms of revenue,
what was the most amount of money that you
ever made in a single year at your company?
About $400 million.
$400 million.
That's a lot of money.
What was your secret to selling
in a competitive industry like construction?
A lot of construction companies.
How did you sell and
close massive multi-million dollar deals?
You sell by doing the right job.
That's the best three-dimensional
business card you could have.
Got to go.
What's that?
What's the business card?
No.
A three-dimensional business card.
The work product you deliver.
And last message to somebody trying
to become wealthy and financially free today.
If you could give them one last chance.
Honest.
Just as importantly, keep your clients
satisfied and put your family first.
Thank you so much, my friend.
Are you a believer in God?
Of course.
How important has faith been for you throughout your career?
At the top of the list.
Yeah.
And how about risk?
How important was it for you
to take risk at an early age?
It was easy.
You know, I didn't have anything to lose.
I could always put my tools
on if it didn't work out.
Thank you, my friend.
Have a great day.
Wow, bro.
What's that?
His name's James?
James, yeah.
I follow you, bro.
Thank you, bro.
Appreciate that.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So we ran after my guy
and we ended up getting the interview.
It turns out he runs one of the
largest construction companies in all of New York City.
They did over $400 million in a single year.
But my biggest takeaway from that interview
was when he said the importance of integrity
and honor in business.
If you don't keep your word
in business, you have no business.
Great interview out here in
New York City on Wall Street.
Let's go get this next
one and keep this video rolling.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Yes.
Yeah?
It's fun.
What do you do for a
living out here in New York City?
I don't know what you mean, man.
Like, what do you do for a living?
What industry do you work in?
How long have you been on Wall Street for?
40 years.
Let me ask you this real quick.
I started a channel at the University of Texas.
I grew it to 5 million followers.
Hook them.
Yes, sir.
I go all over the country just asking
people a couple quick questions on their best advice
to the younger generation.
I get just one minute of your time real quick.
I promise you it'll be worth it.
I've interviewed Mark Cuban, the
president of Nike, CEO of Frito-Lay.
Real quick.
Awesome.
What's the greatest lesson that you've
learned about money throughout your career?
As somebody who works on Wall Street,
what's something that you've learned that 99% of
society does not know about money?
Save every penny you can.
Can you save your way to wealth,
though, or do you have to invest it?
Save every penny you can.
You invest your money?
Of course, but save your money.
How old are you?
I'm 64.
When you're younger, you think money's going to
grow on trees, save every penny you can.
You said that you had-
I always say, what are three words you
would give your younger self to save more money?
Let me ask you this, because you
said that you had been broke before.
What was that turning point
for you towards financial freedom?
Fear of failure.
Number one motivation of man.
What's the most common mistake that you see
business owners make or people make with their
money that prevents them from creating-
Invest with friends or family.
Yeah?
Last one for you real quick.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I was probably 35.
Have you ever met a billionaire before?
Yes, several.
What do billionaires do with their
money differently from 99% of other people?
They take emotion out of it.
What was the hardest skill for
you to master in the business world?
It's very competitive on Wall Street.
What are you-
Communication.
Speak the truth.
How important is it to keep your word in business?
You won't last very long if you don't.
If you don't?
I love that.
If you don't keep your word, you won't last.
Any last words to the younger
generation aspiring to become successful like yourself?
You've given them some amazing advice.
Work hard at school, have fun, and get ready.
It's a long slog.
I always tell people, tell my kids, make sure
you have a five and a 10 year plan.
If you're going to go to work for
a company, they don't give a shit about you.
Start your own business.
Companies don't care.
What type of company do you run?
Finance.
Are you raising money or what are you doing?
Industry analysis.
Auto industry.
Seriously, good luck.
In terms of revenue, what was the most amount
of money you ever made in a single year?
I don't know that.
Could you give me a range maybe?
In the millions.
In the millions?
Your secret to sales.
The honor.
We caught another Wall Street mogul on the run.
What did he say is his secret to creating
wealth that he's passing on to his kids to
become truly successful and
financially free in today's world?
You cannot work for another person.
You can't be working for the
big man and taking a paycheck.
You got to find ways to
create money and work for yourself.
Buy back your time, delegate, and that's how
you can create true financial freedom in today's
world.
Great interview, man.
Entrepreneurship is the way to go.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Multiple times.
Yeah?
Quick question for you.
What do you do for living
out here in New York City?
I work on Wall Street.
How long have you been in finance for?
15, 16 years.
Yeah?
I go all over the country just asking successful
people how they made it for the younger generation.
Can I get just one
minute of your time real quick?
Yeah.
So, let's say you teach a lesson about money.
You teach somebody that the wealthy people
know that most people do not know.
One lesson about money 99% of people don't know.
Money got to keep moving.
In order for it to grow, in order for
it to work for you, it has to keep moving.
Yeah.
Putting it in a bank, under
your mattress, never going to work.
It's got to keep moving.
Investments.
Yeah.
Can I get just one minute of
your time real quick for some questions?
Yeah.
What was the worst financial decision
that you made throughout your career?
Oh, man.
Getting married, man.
My divorce wiped me out.
It was terrible.
Marriage is a business.
I didn't look at it like that.
I was like, oh, I'm in love.
It's a business.
And if you don't look at it like that,
that could be one of the worst financial mistakes
you make.
I'm being honest.
Right.
Being very blunt.
Wiped me out.
Had to start all over from scratch.
But the beauty of it is once you have
it in you internally to build, you have the dog
in you to fight in you, it doesn't matter.
You'll always rebuild.
It's not about losing it.
Anybody listening, it's not about losing it.
Because if you have the dog in
you, you can fight and bring it back.
What it's really about is this.
It's about recovery time.
See, if you lose it at 20,
you're probably in your early 20s, mid 20s.
It's okay.
You have recovery time.
If you lose it at 25,
it'll be 46 in two months.
If you lose it in your 40s, your mid
30s, it's terrible because you don't have the same
recovery rate as someone who's 20 or 19 or 25.
So also they say you are the sum
total of the five people you hang around with.
So be careful of the people you have around you.
Be very selective because you are the sum
total of the people you hang around with.
So those are some of the big mistakes we make.
A lot of times people
try to use socializing for networking.
You're really not networking.
You just want to be social.
And just to be social, to
be social is a waste of time.
Anytime I look at it.
Like if you have.
If you're interacting with someone like I'm
interacting with you, there must be a reason
why we're interacting.
There's a bartering, right?
There's an exchange.
What am I getting out of talking to you?
Some exposure, maybe some likes, which I
really don't care about, but that's the reality,
right?
What are you getting a token out of it?
Right?
Some information.
Right.
So anytime you interact with someone, you
must always ask yourself, what's, what are
we exchanging now real quick before we
go last thing, the universe teaches us this.
What do you do every day?
We breathe, we inhale and we exhale.
You take in the oxygen and
you give out the carbon dioxide, right?
And the trees, your environment takes in
the dioxide and gives you back oxygen.
There's a bartering between you and the,
the, the, the universe, the ecosystem, inhale,
exhale, contract, expand, contract, expand.
So with everything in life, you've got
to apply that science to your life.
Like what is the exchange here?
So the people you interact with, what are they?
What's what's the bartering?
What are they?
Are they an asset?
Is it a liability?
What are we exchanging here?
Those are the mistakes that you got to avoid.
What's the deepest life quote that you've ever heard?
Okay.
Right now.
Don't go, don't go anywhere.
I've got it right here.
This is how committed I am to this quote.
Reality is merely an illusion, albeit
a very persistent one by Albert Einstein.
And I'm not lying.
Look, it's right here on my phone.
My screensaver.
I always use that to remind me that
reality is an illusion, although, and albeit a very
persistent one.
None of this, I could curse.
All right, Paul, none of this shit is real.
It's all an illusion, albeit a very persistent one.
And that's what makes it
a reality because it's so persistent.
And that's Albert Einstein.
That's not mine.
That's amazing.
Thank you so much for your time.
Hard Knocks family.
Wall Street has been amazing so far.
We're on our way to go to our next
interview right now, but I've got a very special announcement
to make.
A couple of weeks ago, we recently launched.
Yeah.
We launched our official entrepreneur community known
as the School of Mentors, and the community
has already hit over a thousand members because
for the people that join, you will have the
ability to hop on live calls, ask your
questions and get directly mentored from the multimillionaires
and the billionaires that I interview
on this channel every single week.
You'll be able to talk to them about
your career, your life, and the businesses that
you're starting and growing.
You do not want to miss out on this
opportunity because it's once in a lifetime and the price
is only $37 a month.
Once we hit 2000 members, the price is going up.
So to join today, click the link
down in the description of this video.
I can't wait to see you on the inside,
but with that being said, let's go get this next
interview.
Nice to meet you.
Yes, sir.
You're the Wall Street man.
What's your nickname?
I am the Einstein of Wall Street.
The Einstein of Wall Street.
This is incredible.
What industry did you decide to pursue a career in?
I decided to pursue a career in many industries.
One of them is finance.
Obviously, I've been a trader on the
floor of the stock exchange for 137 years.
I went to high school with George Washington.
I was here for the
inauguration and that's what I do.
Let me ask you this.
My man.
How old are you now?
I've been 55 for 10 years.
Stop counting.
No, I'm 55.
He's 55.
Yeah, it's all a function of 55.
You know what?
Age is not that important either.
You know, for me, I'm on
the board of five different companies.
I run seven companies.
I trade a half a billion
dollars a day of stock in there.
Today, how did my day?
You'd be amazed.
I did two TV shows, four podcasts, two YouTube videos.
I traded the market till four o'clock
and I'm coming to talk to you.
And now you're doing an
interview with the school of thought.
And there you go.
And I'm doing an interview with you.
So there's no end what you can do with the...
End of the...
There's energy and love for what you're doing.
Eight out of 10 businesses that start,
they won't make it past five years.
What's the most common mistake that you
see business owners make that prevents them from
scaling and having that longevity like yourself?
People fall in love with an
idea and they don't necessarily look at...
It's important to have...
You know, Marcus Limonis, he's a billionaire
who invests in young people's company, talks
about people, process, product, and profits, right?
People need to really identify whether their idea
and their business is going to be profitable,
right?
And it's going to be able to employ other
people and not just fall in love with an idea
because not every business is going to work.
You've really got to examine it
and see, is it going to work?
And if it works, pursue it.
If it doesn't, don't be so in love with yourself
and your idea that you lose sight of the long
game.
In other words, you're going to
kind of detach that emotion from it.
A hundred percent.
Same thing with the stock market.
You know, I teach people that you should trade
the market and people will fall in love with
the trade.
You know, we'll, we'll get wrapped up in
their own ego and not really understand how many
got bored.
They're just taking a profit.
So that's important.
What has been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Oh, I don't ever talk about money
because money is really not that important.
If you look at the internet,
some people say I'm worth $1.8 billion.
If you were to ask my family, they'd go,
if I, if that's true, they'd like to know where
it is.
So I don't, money is really, you know, people will
ask me if I'm rich and I will say, absolutely.
I'm rich.
I have a really great family.
I have a job that I love.
I'm able to, you know, for me, it's
not important to die with the most toys.
That's really not that important.
At the end of the game, if I can
motivate, inspire and empower other people to be their
best self, then I'm a rich person.
The cash part, look, cash does equal freedom.
It doesn't equal happiness.
We know that there are a
lot of miserable millionaires out there.
So the money part is not that
important, but surely it's something that you need.
What's the best industry people should
be looking to get into right now?
I talk to young people all the time and
I would say to them, walk around your school
and look at what phone they're on,
what computer they use, what shoes they wear.
What social media they're on and what
they do in their spare time, right?
Because we are the greatest consumer generation of all time.
We are also the most loyal consumers, right?
We love Starbucks.
We love Apple.
We love Nike.
We love all these things.
And so find companies that you love, the
people, the process, the product and the profitability
and go after that, right?
Do your homework.
Don't look for the shortcut.
It's not about a get rich quick scheme.
Thank you so much for your time.
My pleasure, man.
Hard Knocks family.
That is a wrap on today's video.
Wall Street went crazy, you guys.
But I want to thank you.
I want you to like and subscribe for
amazing content we've got coming very, very soon.
And as I mentioned earlier, our community, the
School of Mentors is only $37 a month
where you can get mentored directly
from the multimillionaires and the billionaires we
interview every single week on this channel.
You'll also get access to exclusive masterclasses
and content I've been filming with the most
successful business owners in the entire world.
So to join today, click the link down in
the description of this video because like I said,
the price is going up as
soon as we hit 2000 members.
You will not want to miss
on this once in a lifetime opportunity.
Bye.
I can't wait to see you on the inside.
And with that being said, we'll
see you guys in the next video.